Grant, Alice Papers /3005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Alice Grant Papers
1964-1970
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Grant, Alice
/3005
10 cubic feet
10 linear ft.
Administrative papers.
Alice Grant's photocopied clippings. Fact-finding and arbitration concerning Rochester, NY teachers, firemen, bus strike, Kodak employees, and public employees.
3071039
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
CB, January 14, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 14, 2016
Biographical / Historical
Alice Grant was a labor educator and staff member of the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University.
Grant earned her B.A. from Wells College and an M.A. from Cornell University. She worked as education director for the Rochester Joint Board of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA) before joining the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations as director of the Rochester Extension office in 1963. Grant held that position until she passed away on November 17, 1988, at the age of 66.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4095: Alice Grant Additional Records
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Grant, Alice, 1922-1988.
3071039
- Rochester Bus Strike, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Rochester Teachers, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  Newspaper articles
- Rochester Teachers, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Rochester Teachers, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Rochester Teachers, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  May through December, 1968.
- Rochester Teachers, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  January through May, 1968.
- Rochester Teachers, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Firemen (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Kodak: Fight dispute (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Policemen (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Public employees (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Public employees (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Public employees, Monroe County (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Rochester bus strike, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Fact-finding and arbitration concerning the buffalo area (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Includes Penfield teachers (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Utica Teachers Association and Board of Education of the City of Utica School District (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Includes FERB fact-finding and arbitration from various locations, together with their unions and/or workers
- Fact-finding and arbitration from various locations, unions and/or types of workers (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Various unions, conferences, programs (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Various unions, conferences, programs (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Various unions, conferences, programs (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Various unions, conferences, programs (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Various unions, conferences, programs (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Various unions, conferences, programs (Box 10, Folder 1)